http://www.lyricmania.com/privacypolicy.html

Lyric Mania Privacy Policy
Viewing the privacy policy at lyric mania
Privacy Policy
Personal Information
LyricMania.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our web site. In order to enhance your experience at our sites we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. We may ask for your name, e-mail address, zip code, and country. The more information you share with us (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to enhance and customize your experience on our sites.
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by LyricMania.com as outlined in this privacy policy. LyricMania.com does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third party unless specified.
IP address and logging
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).
Third Party Advertising
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit LyricMania.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.
Cookies
Some ads displayed may come from our servers. Ads loading from our servers may also contain cookies, the purpose of these cookies is just to introduce and select the proper advertisements to be shown for your interests. We only have access to information of visiting frequencies of our visitors from cookies you might receive while viewing ads from our servers.
Third Party Cookies
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
Disclaimer
This is an information tool provided by at no charge to the user.
LyricMania.com makes no warranties, expressed or implied, for the services we provide. LyricMania.com will not be held responsible for any damages you or your business may suffer from using LyricMania.com services. LyricMania.com will not be held responsible for any interruptions, delays, failures, inaccuracies, or typographical errors.
LyricMania.com does not represent or warrant that the Service or the server that makes it available, are free of viruses or other harmful components. LyricMania.com does not warrant or represent that the use or the results of the use of the Service or the materials made available as part of the Service will be correct, accurate, timely, or otherwise reliable.
LyricMania.com realizes that there are thousands of illegally distributed copyrighted material on the Internet. All the lyrics listed on this site are property of their respective owners and are strictly for educational or personal use only. Commercial use is prohibited without the owners' consent. LyricMania.com is a not-for-profit resource. All advertising proceeds are used to maintain its servers. LyricMania.com does NOT endorse the distribution of copyrighted content. When you download or use lyrics from LyricMania.com web site you do so with the understanding that LyricMania.com and its operators will not be held accountable or responsible for violations of copyright or intellectual property laws that may occur as a result of your action.
Liability
It is LyricMania.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, LyricMania.com will immediately disable and remove lyrics in question.
Artist
Song
Top Lyrics Sites
Free MP3 Downloads
Song Lyrics
Free MP3 Albums
Music Lyrics
Lyrics Search
All lyrics presented may be copyrighted by the respective owners, artists and labels.
Privacy Policy | Lyric Mania |
Lyrics
